How to change the user interface
Hello, everyone.
Through this video, you will learn about the new features in Marvelous Designer 11.
First, let's take a look at the changes in the user interface.
In Marvelous Designer 11, you can switch the main page of General or Store through the label bar.
You can see these two labels on the far left.
The General page is used to create clothes.
By selecting the Store label, you can view the products sold on the Marvelous Designer website.
Now you can buy clothes directly in the software without visiting the website via the browser.
Using the previous version of Marvelous Designer, you can only open two work areas windows at the same time.
In the new version, you can select the window display by clicking on the lower right corner.
You can select the window display by clicking on the lower right corner of the window.
You can also display four work areas windows at the same time.
By clicking the Remake button, you can go back to the default settings.
By clicking the drop-down menu at the top of the work area window, you can choose a suitable mode based on the usage mode.
At the top right corner of each window, you can find the Copy button.
These pop-up windows can be dragged to the two windows on the screen and placed at will.
The two windows can be closed, hidden or assembled with other windows.
Click the arrow button in the upper left corner to hide the window.
When the window is hidden, it will appear in the form of a label bar on both sides.
If you click the label, the window will appear again.
Click the X button in the upper right corner of the window to close the window.
Any pop-up window can be dragged to the existing window to merge them.
Their names will appear in the form of a label at the bottom of the window.
By clicking the label, you can view each window in the group.
You can switch modes by clicking the drop-down menu at the top of the window.
The user can use multiple modes in multiple windows at the same time.
If you open multiple 3D windows at the same time, you can use different tools in each window.
The window on the 2D version will be linked to the 3D window you choose, so the tool you use will be displayed in the 2D window.
For example, if you click on a fake needle tool in a 3D window, you can see the 3D window in the 2D version.
You can edit or create a fake needle in the 2D window because they are linked.
Similarly, if you choose the move tool in the 3D window, the 2D window will also switch to the selected version tool.
However, you can only open a 2D window at the same time.
This means that if you change a window to a 2D window through the drop-down menu, the original 2D window will be contrasted with it.
This means that if you change a window to a 2D window, the original 2D window will be contrasted with it.
Once you choose a new window law for the man.
You can select the 3D window you want to create.
Click on Managingzing.
You can also add a stamp to the number of windows left.
The window layout can be reviewed by just clicking on the icon in thewh tv screen.
Click on Managingzing on the remaining windows.
You can browse through it on the main page.
You can also select more than one window type as a unit of the window şöyle
In Marvelous Designer 11, more tools are integrated into the tool group.
To make it easier to use, click on the cutout line on the pull-down menu or press the Enter key, and you can open the tool group in a spring form.
Any main menu with a cutout line can also be opened in spring form.
By clicking and dragging on the tool bar on the far left, you can open the tool group in a spring form.
To open the tool group in a spring form, you can click and drag on the tool bar on the far left, and you can open the tool group in a spring form.
From the tool group, you can choose the position and the position of the tool bar.
You can choose the position and the position of the tool bar.
You can choose to hold the tool at one side of the tool bar and control the others at the other side.
You can choose to display or hide the tool bar
Finally, click on the arrow at the bottom of the interface
You can open or close the animation editor
You can choose to display or hide the tool bar